question_data = [

    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Clefairy was intended to be Ash&#039;s starting Pok&eacute;mon in the pilot episode of "
                    "the cartoon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In the &quot;Melancholy of Haruhi Suzumiya&quot; series, the narrator goes by the "
                    "nickname Kyon.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In Kill La Kill, the weapon of the main protagonist is a katana. ",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "The anime &quot;Lucky Star&quot; follows the story of one girl who is unaware she is God.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf "
                    "Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Golden Darkness is sent to kill Lala Deviluke.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Ash&#039;s Pikachu refuses to go into a pokeball.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "In Chobits, Hideki found Chii in his apartment.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
        "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan / Case Closed!)",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    }

]
